Terms of Service

Last Updated: November 14, 2024

Welcome to the website of the Sri Lanka Aikido Association. By accessing and using our website at https://lahiruprabodha.github.io/aikido, you agree to the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully before using the site.

1. Acceptance of Terms
By accessing or using our website, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please discontinue use of our website.

2. Use of Website Content
All content on our website, including text, graphics, images, and multimedia, is the property of the Sri Lanka Aikido Association or is used with permission from third parties. This content is provided for informational purposes only.

Prohibited Actions:
You agree not to:

Reproduce, distribute, or exploit any content on this site without our express written permission.
Use the site in a way that could damage, disable, or impair its functionality or interfere with other users.
Attempt to gain unauthorized access to any part of the site, other accounts, or networks.
3. User Conduct
You agree to use our website responsibly and for lawful purposes only. You are responsible for any content you share on or through the site, including adhering to any applicable local, state, national, or international laws.

4. Links to Third-Party Websites
Our website may contain links to external websites for your convenience. These third-party websites are not under our control, and we are not responsible for their content or practices. We encourage you to review their terms and policies, as we do not endorse or assume responsibility for any third-party websites.

5. Disclaimer of Warranties
Our website and its content are provided on an "as-is" basis. We do not warrant that the content is accurate, complete, or current. To the fullest extent permitted by law, the Sri Lanka Aikido Association disclaims all warranties, express or implied, related to this website, including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.

6. Limitation of Liability
To the maximum extent permitted by law, the Sri Lanka Aikido Association shall not be liable for any damages arising from your use of, or inability to use, this website or its content. This includes, but is not limited to, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, and consequential damages.

7. Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless the Sri Lanka Aikido Association, its officers, directors, employees, and affiliates from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, losses, or expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, arising out of or in any way connected with your use of the website, your violation of these Terms, or your infringement of any third-party rights.

8. Changes to Terms of Service
We reserve the right to update or modify these Terms of Service at any time without prior notice. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting to this page. Your continued use of the website after any changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Terms.

9. Governing Law
These Terms of Service shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [Country/State], without regard to its conflict of law principles. Any legal action or proceeding related to this website shall be brought exclusively in the courts located in [City/Region].

10. Contact Information
If you have any questions or concerns about these Terms of Service, please contact us at:

Sri Lanka Aikido Association
No. 40, Ekamuth Uyana, Gonamadiththa Road, Piliyandala
Phone: +94773291201
Email: lahiru.wickramarathne@outlook.com